http://www.isu.org/quick-links-sep/privacy-policy

ISU
Home
Quick Links
Privacy Policy
Data and its protection are becoming increasingly more important to individuals and enterprises. The European Union (EU) enacted the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) which will be enforced starting May 25, 2018. The GDPR is designed to give EU residents better control over their personal data regardless of where data is sent, processed or stored by establishing one set of data protection rules across the EU.
The International Skating Union is committed to protect your personal data and committed to GDPR compliance having members from the EU and being active on EU territory.
This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.
We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to media@isu.ch
or by writing to: International Skating Union - Avenue Juste-Olivier 17, 1006 Lausanne - Switzerland.
WHO ARE WE?
The International Skating Union (ISU), founded in 1892, is the oldest governing international winter sport federation and the exclusive international sport federation recognized by the International Olympic Committee (ISU) administering the sports of Figure Skating (Single & Pair Skating and Ice Dance), Synchronized Skating, Speed Skating and Short Track Speed Skating worldwide. The objectives of the ISU are to regulate, govern, promote and develop its sports on the basis of friendship and mutual understanding between athletes. Currently three ISU disciplines are included in the Olympic Winter Games program (Figure Skating, Speed Skating and Short Track Speed Skating). The ISU is located in Lausanne, Switzerland.
SERVICES COVERED BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy applies to all digital services such as websites, newsletters, registration systems, or online business resources (including our extranet) offered on www.isu.org website and other digital properties created and/or operated by the ISU (collectively the “Services”).
REGISTRATION
Our content is generally available on the Services without the need to register as a user. However, certain personalization options, transactions or services (such as e-commerce, newsletters, professional services or event registration services) offered on our website and other digital properties require that you register and provide certain information about you.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
The personal information we collect might include your name, address, email address, IP address, and information regarding what pages are accessed and when. If you purchase a product from us, your card information is not held by us, it is collected by our third-party payment processor 2Checkout, who specialize in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions, as explained below. We will collect information about you in different situations, for instance when you register on our Services, when you contact us or when you request a service from us. We may also collect certain information when you visit our Services (also as non-registered user), through cookies, pixels and similar technologies.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
We use the personal information we collect to deliver and promote our Services to communicate with you and to provide you with the Services which you have requested. We also make available our content on a variety of third party platforms like Facebook, Twitter or YouTube. These platforms are governed by their own terms and conditions and privacy policies that we strongly recommend you read.
THE INFORMATION WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES
We will only provide your information to third parties in the following circumstances: (1) we share certain user information with our affiliates and service providers who work with us to offer you the Services; (2) we may share your information with authorities or third parties when we believe that we have a legal obligation to do so; and (3) we may share your information with third parties when you have given us your prior authorization to do so.
HOW TO LIMIT OR DELETE YOUR INFORMATION
The ISU is also working on ways to make it easier for you to review and correct your information. If you change email address, or if any other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, please contact the ISU.
SECURITY PRECAUTIONS IN PLACE TO PROTECT THE LOSS, MISUSE OR ALTERATION OF YOUR INFORMATION
When you provide us with personal information, we take steps to ensure that it is treated securely. Any sensitive information (such as credit or debit card details) is encrypted and protected as per the 2Checkout policies.
Non-sensitive details (your email address etc.) are transmitted normally over the Internet, and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
USE OF 'COOKIES'
Like many other websites, the ISU website uses cookies. 'Cookies' are small pieces of information sent by an organization to your computer and stored on your hard drive to allow that website to recognize you when you visit. They collect statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and do not identify you as an individual. You can block cookies and similar technologies by configuring the functionalities of your internet browser.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website may contain links to other websites run by other organizations and providers. This privacy policy applies only to www.isu.org‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites.
16 OR UNDER
We are concerned to protect the privacy of children aged 16 or under. If you are aged 16 or under‚ please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide us with personal information.
TRANSFERRING YOUR INFORMATION OUTSIDE OF EUROPE
As part of the Services offered to you through www.isu.org, the information which you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Union (“EU”). By way of example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside of the EU. These countries may not have similar data protection laws. By submitting your personal data, you are agreeing to this transfer, storing or processing. If you use our services while you are outside the EU, your information may be transferred outside the EU in order to provide you with those services.
